We've done the variation exercise.
我们已经完成了变化练习。
The forward exercise.
向前运动。
Now we're going to do improvisation.
现在我们要做即兴创作。
Remember I told you improvisation means that you speak without thinking.
记住我告诉过你即兴创作意味着你不假思索地说话。
This is very important.
这个非常重要。
If you want to get used to that feeling of speaking freely in conversation without feeling like where
如果你想习惯那种在谈话中畅所欲言的感觉，而不是在哪里
are my words I can't find my words.
是我的话我找不到我的话。
Well you probably can't find your words because you're not used to finding them in conversation.
嗯，你可能找不到你的话，因为你不习惯在谈话中找到它们。
And it's as simple as that.
就这么简单。
You have to do something in order to be good at it.
你必须做一些事情才能擅长它。
So in the improvisation exercise you need to speak continuously cannot right this one speak continuously.
所以在即兴练习中你需要连续说话不能对这个连续说话。
Write down a word and then whatever that reminds you of.
写下一个词，然后写下任何让你想起的东西。
Start talking about it and then go and go for about a minute maybe two minutes if you can just talk.
开始谈论它，然后继续讨论大约一分钟，如果你能谈谈的话，也许两分钟。
Doesn't have to be perfect.
不一定要完美。
It's not going to be perfect.
它不会是完美的。
I'm going to do it in a moment.
我马上就去做。
I'm probably going to say some things that sound a little I don't know silly maybe I don't know.
我可能会说一些听起来有点我不知道的傻话，也许我不知道。
I don't know what I'm going to say it's going to be improvisation.
我不知道我要说什么，这将是即兴创作。
OK.
好的。
So this is an extremely important exercise.
所以这是一个非常重要的练习。
Always record it.
总是记录下来。
Pushed the record button on your phone whatever.
随便按了手机上的录音键。
Just make sure it's recorded so that you can listen back to it and see how you did.
只需确保它已被录制，以便您可以回听并了解您的表现。
OK.
好的。
So choose a word that has some meaning in your life.
所以选择一个对你的生活有意义的词。
Don't choose a word like of or in doesn't have much meaning inside of it.
不要选择像of或in这样的词，里面没有太多意义。
Choose a word like wild life.
选择一个像野生动物这样的词。
And I'm just going to start speaking.
我要开始发言了。
I promise you I have not planned this OK.
我向你保证，我没有计划好。
And I'm going to use the first take of this.
我将使用这个的第一个镜头。
That means I'm not going to cut this and try many many tries.
这意味着我不会削减这个并尝试很多次尝试。
I want you to get a feeling for the real one.
我想让你感受一下真实的感觉。
This is my first attempt.
这是我的第一次尝试。
I'm only going to record this one time and I'm going to talk about wildlife.
我只记录一次，我将谈论野生动物。
You can do the same thing.
你可以做同样的事情。
Use wildlife or use another word.
使用野生动物或使用其他词。
Choose a word like marriage or a word like literature or dentistry.
选择像婚姻这样的词，或者像文学或牙科这样的词。
I like to use subjects because you can talk about those things and connect it to your life.
我喜欢使用主题，因为您可以谈论这些事情并将其与您的生活联系起来。
So here we go.
所以我们开始吧。
So when I grew up I was basically raised to know how to make things.
所以当我长大后，我基本上就知道如何制作东西了。
And that's because I was raised in the countryside so I would often go out into the woods and I would
那是因为我在农村长大，所以我经常到树林里去，我会
make forts and I would make tree houses and I would like to find things in the river.
做堡垒，我会做树屋，我想在河里找东西。
And it gave me a real appreciation for nature and for wildlife.
它让我对自然和野生动物产生了真正的欣赏。
And I think that's one of the reasons why I really care so much about making sure that human activities
我认为这就是为什么我非常关心确保人类活动的原因之一
don't have a negative effect on nature and on wildlife.
不会对自然和野生动物产生负面影响。
So take for example the animals in Africa which are endangered because of poaching there.
因此，以非洲因偷猎而濒临灭绝的动物为例。
There are many people who who want for whatever reason certain things certain products that can be made
有很多人出于某种原因想要某些可以制造的产品
from animals like elephant tusks and because there are people who will pay money for that because there
来自象牙之类的动物，因为有些人会为此付钱，因为那里
are people who will buy that they then are supporting an economy where a poacher is a person who hunts
是那些会买东西的人，然后他们正在支持偷猎者就是打猎的人的经济
or kills animals like elephants illegally will will kill an elephant to get its tusks and it's causing
或非法杀死像大象这样的动物会杀死大象以获得它的象牙，这会导致
these animals to be endangered.
这些动物濒临灭绝。
So I think because of my my childhood in nature and studying animals watching animals and playing outside
所以我想是因为我在大自然中的童年和研究动物看动物和在外面玩耍
I think I have a deep appreciation and I think a lot of other people do too.
我想我很感激，我想很多其他人请也这样做。
And I think that really we have to do something and take action in order to to actually protect animals
我认为我们真的必须做一些事情并采取行动才能真正保护动物
especially animals and plants to be honest which are endangered.
尤其是濒临灭绝的动物和植物。
So let's take elephants I mean elephants are being killed very often in Africa and there are some people
所以让我们以大象为例，我的意思是大象在非洲经常被杀，有些人
who actually do do things to protect them.
谁真正做事情来保护他们。
Sharks as well.
鲨鱼也一样。
There are things that can be done to protect these animals.
可以采取一些措施来保护这些动物。
One of the things that I think is probably good for anybody to do is donate to organizations who are
我认为可能对任何人都有好处的一件事就是向那些
actually fighting illegal poaching.
实际打击非法偷猎。
And just by donating to those organizations they can then bring on more people and get to know the maybe
只需向这些组织捐款，他们就可以吸引更多人并了解可能
local culture so that they can try to have a real impact because if the elephants are gone like the
当地文化，以便他们可以尝试产生真正的影响，因为如果大象像
rhino is gone now one of the rhino species is gone.
犀牛消失了，现在其中一种犀牛物种消失了。
Then what's the point of being alive if we don't have animals to appreciate.
如果我们没有动物可以欣赏，那么活着还有什么意义。
OK.
好的。
I'm going to stop there.
我要停在那里。
So that was me just going.
所以这就是我要去的地方。
I didn't have anything in mind.
我什么都没想。
I didn't have anything planned.
我没有任何计划。
Just talking and maybe I repeated myself a few times when you don't have a clear structure when you
只是说话，也许我重复了几次当你没有清晰的结构时
don't have an outline.
没有大纲。
It tends to happen when you're in conversation with friends.
当您与朋友交谈时，它往往会发生。
It's very easy to kind of repeat yourself or focus on something too much or whatever.
重复自己或过多地关注某事或其他事情很容易。
That's not the point of this exercise.
这不是本练习的重点。
The point of this exercise is for you to get used to the feeling of speaking freely without stopping
这个练习的重点是让你习惯那种说不完的感觉
so that when you need to have those conversations when you need to explain yourself you feel comfortable
这样当您需要进行这些对话时，当您需要解释自己时，您会感到很自在
and confident to do so.
并有信心这样做。
So try the exercise where you do variations try the forward exercise and try the improvisation exercise
所以尝试你做变化的练习尝试前向练习并尝试即兴练习
and for that one.
和那个。
Make sure you speak.
确保你说话。
Make sure you record so that you can listen to it again.
确保您录制，以便您可以再次收听。
So to practice this.
所以要练习这个。
Number one for the forward exercise.
向前练习的第一名。
Start with these four.
从这四个开始。
And then once you've done these for a few times try your own.
然后一旦你完成了这些几次尝试你自己的。
Write down your own four words go to five go to six then for the improv exercise.
写下你自己的四个字去五去六然后进行即兴练习。
You can try these two fake products and parenting.
你可以试试这两个假货和育儿。
OK just two topics you can use but then after that pick your own topics.
好的，您可以使用两个主题，但之后选择您自己的主题。
It's not hard.
这并不难。
Just choose anything and talk about it for the other one.
只需选择任何东西并为另一个谈论它。
The variation all you have to do is find a paragraph from a story find a paragraph from an article for
您所要做的就是从故事中找到一段从文章中找到一段
example and make variations of that.
示例并对其进行更改。
See how many different ways you can say it.
看看你可以用多少种不同的方式说出来。
All right.
好的。
Good luck and I hope that these exercises help to improve your ability to think in English and also
祝你好运，我希望这些练习有助于提高你的英语思考能力
improve your speaking habits.
改善你的说话习惯。
Good luck.
祝你好运。